义务教育教科书五四学制英语六年级上册，由上海教育出版社出版。
New Star Middle School in Shanghai welcomes the new grade 6 students.
In class, students are introducing themselves.
Hi, I'm Lu Yao.
In my free time, I like running and playing the piano.
Hello, my name is Wang Yiming.
I like playing basketball and taking photos.
Hello, I'm Li Bailing.
I love singing and writing.
Hi, everyone.
I'm Lin Dong.
I love sports and science.
Nice to meet you all.
It's a school day.
Students are getting ready for class.
It's eight in the morning.
I've got my red scarf ready.
The school bell's ringing.
My pens, books and notebooks are missing.
Where is my bag?
Is this your bag, Yiming?
It's on my desk.
Yes, it's mine.
It's heavy.
What's in it?
He opens his bag, takes out everything and puts them on his desk.
Let me see.
There are five books, three notebooks, a pencil case, some paper, an English-Chinese dictionary.
This is your secret to English learning, isn't it?
Wang Yiming is reading emails from his friends.
From Lisa to Yiming Harry.
Subject, hi from London.
Hi, pals.
How are you?
I'm back in London now.
When will you be free?
Let's have a video chat and I'll show you around my new home.
Best, Lisa.
From Harry to Lisa Yiming.
Subject, hi from London.
Hi, Lisa.
Glad to hear from you.
Yiming and I are in the same middle school now.
We'll be free every Friday from 3 to 5 p.
m.
Beijing time.
Let's chat, Harry.
Students are talking about what they can do with English.
I can read and write the 26 letters in the English alphabet.
What about you?
I can use a dictionary to look up new words.
How about you?
I can say numbers, days of the week and school things in English.
And you?
I can introduce myself in English.
I know you can.
I can understand simple picture stories and cartoons in English.
What about you?
I know the English names of some countries.
How about you?
I know how to make sentences with words.
Try me.
I know when to use hello, yes, no, sorry, thank you, please.
Goodbye, okay, help, and I don't know, wait, I mean I know.